http://www.kingcord.com/aboutus.php#privacy

SOLITAIRE GAME
Customer Service | 877 474 8864 | Shopping Cart | My Account
Warranties
Our company has been contributing to your outdoor seating comfort for over three decades, by making the highest-quality rope hammocks, with our own braided soft-spun polyester cord. Unique among all rope hammocks, our hammocks are highly durable and sensationally comfortable: the gold standard for comfort for well over three decades. That added comfort makes all the difference!
We've augmented --and continue to increase-- the breadth of our products only with similarly high-quality indoor and outdoor furniture: we sell just the best products in their category. Makes life a little easier!
Contact Us:
Customer Service Dept.
Kingcord Hammocks
41 Reynolds Road
Lansdowne, On K0E 1L0
info@Kingcord.com
Tel: 1 877 474 8864
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Security Policy
Shipping
Tracking your Order
Warranties
FAQ
History
"How it's Made"
Gallery & Feedback
Wholesale
Links
Maple Leaf Solitaire
View Larger Map
Warranty:
Each product we sell carries an individual warranty from its manufacturer. Please read it carefully and follow the instructions to ensure you comply with the warranty and are aware of its conditions and lifespan. For instance, upon registration, the Bougainville and Hampton Head hammocks are guaranteed against defects in materials and workmanship for three years from the date of purchase. If during those three years any such defects materialize, the manufacturer will at its discretion replace or repair the hammock. Of course, this guarantee does not cover such factors as normal wear and tear, damage caused by vandalism, pets or wildlife, or prolonged exposure to the elements, e.g. precipitation, humidity. Other products carry shorter or, in some cases, much longer warranties. Look for the information on the specific product's pages.
Return Policy:
We want our customers to be completely satisfied with our products. If for any reason you wish to return a purchase to us, you may do so within 30 days of purchase shipment, upon our authorization. The product should be shipped back prepaid in its original packing and in saleable condition, by ground mail, for credit or refund. Restocking fees apply, and restrictions may apply in case of specially- ordered items.
Please note:
• Please contact us to arrange return authorization: required for all returns.
• Shipping charges are non-refundable.
• There are no refunds after 30 days.
• A 20% restocking fee will be charged on all returned items.
• A lot of our orders are custom orders, and need to be specially ordered from the factory. Custom orders are cancellable within 72 hours of order date. A 20% cancellaton fee will be assessed to any custom order cancelled or returned after 72 hours. Please contact us if you have further questions on this.
• Items must be in good working order and complete with all the original packaging included.
• Items returned in used or altered condition cannot be accepted.
• All returns must be fully insured and shipped with freight charges prepaid by the customer.
Privacy Policy:
We appreciate the trust you place in us, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. This privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it.
We welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact us at:
Kingcord Hammocks
41 Reynolds Road
Lansdowne, ON K0E 1L0
info@kingcord.com
When you place an order with Kingcord.com, we ask you to provide information by filling out and submitting an online form. We ask for your name, email address and the minimum of other personal information we need to complete the transaction. We do not share, sell or trade email addresses, information collected as part of a survey, or specific details about you or your household. We do not contribute to or participate in shared or cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your personal information. We do not release credit card or financial information for use by other companies. For both privacy and security purposes, all transactional information communicated between customers and our Web site is transmitted in an encrypted format, and all credit card information is briefly stored -for less than a day- in a highly secure computing environment until processed, after which it is removed and we retain only the regular hard copy. (See Security below for further details.)
Following is a list of the information we request, and details on how we use this information.
• Checkout. We ask for your name, (email and physical) address
and contact information so we can send you your order, and so we can contact you if we have a question about your order. We ask for credit card information so we can fulfill your order, and so we can provide this information to the companies who process your credit card payment. We do not share your name and address with other companies, or any third parties, except in the case of contact or order information needed to fulfill your order.
• Emails to Kingcord.com. If you have provided your email address to us by sending us an email message, we may follow up on your question via email, but we will not use it to contact you for marketing purposes. We do not share questions or comments provided with any other company.    Order Confirmation and Tracking. After you place an order on our site, you will    receive an email order confirmation. If some of the products you ordered are not in    stock, we will notify you of the estimated shipment date(s) of your order when the    physical order process is initiated. Otherwise, we immediately process the order for    shipment. Upon shipment, we will further send you a shipment confirmation with,    whenever possible, the package tracking information. Please e-Mail us with your questions or comments: we respond to every email we receive.
Links to other sites
We may, from time to time, provide links to a few other quality sites you may enjoy, to increase our internet exposure. These sites operate independently of Kingcord.com and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we advise you to review those policies at any site you visit.
Security:
We understand your concerns about online security. Because we share your concerns, we work hard to keep our site a highly secure ordering environment – so you can shop with confidence.
The result is a Web site that offers you the high level of service, convenience and trustworthiness you should expect in every web shopping experience.
The Secure Order Process:
Using our proprietary e-business software, in conjunction with features built into popular browser software, our site provides advanced security for your online purchases. The following section describes how the secure order process works, from start to finish.
Cookies.
A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on our Web site. We use cookies just to remember what items are in your Shopping Cart. If you have set your browser to refuse cookies, please adjust the settings while shopping on our site, or call us to place your order.
1. Starting Your Order
Every purchase at Kingcord.com is secure, because our entire ordering system is secure. The security features are automatic; you don't need to do anything special to invoke them. As soon as you move from the cart to the checkout pages, you're in a secure environment.
2. Making a Positive ID
Once you've clicked to go to our secure checkout, your browser looks for a digital certificate to confirm that it is communicating with Kingcord.com. At this point you may see a window, which some browsers display when you are about to receive a secure document. It's fine to click "OK" (or "Continue") to proceed – it simply means that you will begin receiving pages in a highly secure encrypted format. Once a positive ID is made, you can securely browse our site or place an order.
We use Thawte (A VeriSign company) software to enable the use of digital certificates. You can click on the Thawte logo to verify that Kingcord.com is a Thawte secure site. For your security, the verification process happens in the background every time you browse between pages or place an order on our site. Your computer and our server communicate in secure mode, sending data back and forth in an encrypted format.
When you place your order, we ask you to enter your credit card information. The encryption features of browser software ensure the security of this data as it is transmitted to our server. Our site makes use of the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol and 128-bit strong encryption to provide the highest level of security available.
3. My Order Is Complete. What Happens Next?
Security measures continue even after you've placed your order, as we process your order in a highly secure computing environment, and immediately upon processing delete your financial information, retaining only a regular hard copy. Once your order is complete, it's perfectly safe for you to continue to browse our site.
Security at Work
The most popular Web browsers, e.g. Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Chrome, Safari, use clear visual symbols to let you know whether or not they are in secure mode. The symbols are usually a version of a padlock. Clicking on the symbols can display the site's security certificate. Another indication that a browser is in secure mode is in the Web site address that your browser displays. The address will begin "http://" in standard, non-secure mode and "https://" in secure mode. The "s" stands for "secure." Please note that the latest versions of browsers have advanced security features, and are free for downloading. Visit their company's Web site for details.
Shipping:
Speed of delivery of product(s) depends on stock status: Those products we have in stock, we ship quickly: within two days. Quick Shipment status is indicated on the product page. If some of the products you ordered are not in stock, we will notify you of the expected shipment date(s) of your order when the physical order process is initiated. We have a fairly simple shipping schedule using ground shipping by Fedex and UPS. Most orders have a single shipping charge for each state or province, but a few items that are oversized or extra heavy will incur oversize charges.Extended Savings on Shipping: Pay a flat fee of $15 on most regular-sized orders over $150. Other orders over $150 get $10 off the regular charges below!
Province Tax Charged Shipping   Oversize Charge
AB MB SK  GST -
5% $25   $40 per OS item
PE  HST -
14% $25   $40 per OS item
BC  GST -
5% $25   $40 per OS item
NT NU YT  GST - 5% $115   $65 per OS item
Visit us at our workshop in the heart of the Thousand Islands, where experienced craftsmen still make each hammock entirely by hand.
Open:  Monday to Friday from 10 to 5;   Saturday from 10 to 2.
Summer Hours: 7 days a week, from 9 to 7.About Us, and Directions to our Store
For retail inquiries and further information on the above products, write, call, or e-mail us:
USA: Box 836  Fineview, NY 13640  Canada: 41 Reynolds Road   Lansdowne, ON K0E 1L0   Call Toll Free: (877) 474 8864  e-Mail : info@kingcord.com
In the neighborhood?
]
Kingcord.com is a secure ordering site, protected by Thawte. We respect your privacy. Copyright © 2017 Kingcord All rights reserved.
